Guide to the
Brown University Library
- 5 MNGW Chapter 5 KB pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-05-27 11:03:21 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-06 12:27:33 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 10 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 10/Date created: 2012-07-05 19:15:16 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-05 19:15:34 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Denver-Twin Cities.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Denver-Twin Cities 2012/Date created: 2012-10-09 10:42:15 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-10-09 10:42:15 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 1 KB Edit Chap 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-15 21:33:01 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-15 22:05:34 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 4 MNGW Chapter 4 KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-05-26 11:06:35 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-09-15 15:27:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Welcome to NYU LGBTQ.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Tao of Sabbath Mitvah Boddhisatva ƒ/Date created: 2009-03-30 16:19:18 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-30 16:19:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Anna Story.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/men women rest of us 07/Date created: 2008-05-20 17:40:10 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-01-16 15:26:23 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW rainbow anarchy trans ruby slippers KB note.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-24 18:33:02 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-25 00:30:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- University of Toledo 10.16.13 schedule.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/U of Toledo 16-10-13/Date created: 2013-10-11 13:50:41 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-10-11 13:51:46 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-2 Borderline Old.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-2 Borderline ƒ/Date created: 2011-01-02 09:20:11 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-01-02 21:00:54 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Uncle Stinky Where.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Copy Edits/Date created: 2013-01-15 14:03:27 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-15 14:32:48 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KBDixonPlaceLaunchPressRelease.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/Date created: 2012-04-18 13:21:17 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-29 22:49:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2 MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-07-15 10:57:17 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 10:57:17 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB pass 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Epilogue/Date created: 2011-09-06 12:06:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-06 12:26:32 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires SFU 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2009-03-05 11:20:12 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-03-06 09:57:14 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- keynote notes beyond the binary.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Articles to Mine for MNGW/Transcending Boundaries Keynote ƒ/Date created: 2011-11-11 20:39:47 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-11-12 09:57:31 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Tao of Mitzvah Sabbath Boddhisatva.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2010-02-02 16:34:37 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-02 16:34:38 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Kate Stay Alive.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Kate Stay Alive/Date created: 2013-03-18 16:05:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-03-18 16:05:52 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB 1st Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Epilogue/Early Epilogue/Date created: 2011-09-05 17:31:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-05 17:31:06 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 3 Let X = X/Date created: 2012-02-11 11:59:18 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-05-24 15:50:15 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- University of Illinois 100212 itinerary.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Univ Illinois Springfield/Date created: 2012-09-29 21:51:12 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-09-29 21:51:12 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/0/8/1/Attachments/180227/1/Date created: 2016-11-08 13:54:15 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-11-08 13:54:15 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Keynote Women-Gender Consoritum.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Keynote Women Gender Studies Consortium/Date created: 2009-11-06 08:16:45 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-11-06 08:24:14 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Present Physicians--Concurrent Medical Care.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Block Center/Date created: 2013-03-03 17:24:16 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-03-03 20:30:22 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- There and Back Again.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/4/8/1/Attachments/184589/2.2/Date created: 2015-10-23 12:04:40 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-23 12:04:40 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 2 Where Is Gender?/Date created: 2012-02-06 14:55:31 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-09 13:44:53 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Author 1st proof AQs (Prelims to Chap 2).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Copy Edits Round 2/Date created: 2013-01-25 11:50:07 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-25 11:50:07 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Aiden Fyre LOR.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/aiden /Date created: 2012-05-04 12:24:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-04 12:44:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB Books Amazon Links pages 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/WordPress Website/Date created: 2016-01-27 21:07:38 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-01-27 21:07:38 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- My White Underwear Story.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Julia Kaplan words/Date created: 2012-08-10 17:32:02 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-09-09 15:16:02 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW if it were KBs notebook.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-23 18:56:08 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-23 18:58:34 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Testing a Theory.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Fictionmania Downloads/Date created: 2010-11-26 21:24:58 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-26 21:28:00 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-2 after the big cut and paste.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-2 Borderline ƒ/Date created: 2011-01-08 16:25:23 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-01-08 16:25:23 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Roz Second Poem.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-01-24 16:12:07 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-24 16:12:07 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB final draft CreatingChange2016.kb.workshop.proposal.pages09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Random Writings That Relate/Creating Change Workshop/creating change workshop attic/Date created: 2015-09-24 13:53:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-09-24 13:53:32 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 07 Cautionary thru Revolutionary.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Workbook Attic/My New Gender Workbook Working by Chapter/Date created: 2012-01-03 16:59:30 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 16:59:30 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 100 GLBT Colleges Contact Info.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Resources and Prospects/Date created: 2009-01-14 13:30:03 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-01-14 13:30:03 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dedication-Acknowledgments.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Date created: 2011-09-11 19:16:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-12 13:46:36 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Treasure Map 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 2 Where Is Gender?/Date created: 2012-02-04 13:16:34 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-06 16:24:04 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Reading with David.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/Memoir Readings/Date created: 2012-04-06 16:39:55 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-06 16:39:55 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 01 Welcome to Your Workbook.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Workbook Attic/My New Gender Workbook Working by Chapter/Date created: 2012-01-03 14:48:34 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 14:48:34 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Payment Letter Nov 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Monthly Payments to IRS/Date created: 2011-11-07 12:16:54 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-11-07 12:18:02 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Acknowledgements.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 0 TOC and Intro/Date created: 2012-07-07 16:40:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-07 18:47:55 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB workshop promo .pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/8D5A1E6A-3871-48CC-B85B-B014FE3DEA28/Tour Venues Booked.mbox/Been There, Done That.mbox/UK Tour Feb 2016.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/6/7/2/Attachments/276898/2/Date created: 2015-12-04 12:52:32 EST-0500Date modified: 2015-12-04 12:52:32 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-4 OK This Is Where It Gets Complicated.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2011-06-21 19:16:59 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-23 14:53:50 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2-6.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2010-01-25 18:18:18 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-27 17:19:17 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- There and Back Again.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/4/8/1/Attachments/184658/1/Date created: 2015-10-23 12:04:41 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-23 12:04:41 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 03 Be All You Can Be, Fuck Your Gender, Love Sex Desire.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Workbook Attic/My New Gender Workbook Working by Chapter/Date created: 2012-01-03 14:57:59 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 14:57:59 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB_Acting_Wkshop_Handout.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Workshop Handouts/Acting Workshop/Date created: 2010-10-22 13:00:58 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-22 13:32:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Bornstein Rider QAF 2012.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Vancouver Queer Arts Festival 2012/Date created: 2012-07-10 14:16:22 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-10 14:16:41 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW rainbow anarchy trans line art ruby slippers KB note.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-25 00:32:13 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-25 00:33:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Author Questionnaire Kate Bornstein.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/0/8/1/Attachments/180503/1/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:54:02 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:54:02 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My Gender Workbook/Chapter Drafts in Pages format/Date created: 2012-02-11 11:59:18 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-14 14:29:41 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Intro All That Jazz.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/6/7/1/Attachments/176901/2/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:53:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:53:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- aftercare.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2011-08-31 12:51:54 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-31 12:51:54 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- molly asks me to marry her.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/Readings for Dixon Place/Date created: 2012-04-29 17:59:11 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-29 17:59:12 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb meds sheet 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2009-06-05 12:37:44 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-06-07 16:02:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- BalladOfLittleJo_by_Kate_B.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Articles to Mine for MNGW/Date created: 2011-01-11 19:29:52 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-01-11 20:42:26 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 2 2.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Now With Beacon/Date created: 2011-08-19 11:54:22 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-19 11:54:22 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Sex, Bullies, and You 2010 Reader.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2010-09-23 02:07:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-09-23 22:38:50 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW chapter 8 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 8 Do Your Gender Mindfully/Date created: 2012-07-04 22:43:41 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-04 22:44:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Payment Letter Oct 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Monthly Payments to IRS/Date created: 2011-10-11 12:44:35 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-10-11 13:25:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 316 HSESITTER INSTRUC 6-11 Cape Cod.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/house-sitting/Date created: 2011-06-13 16:32:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-10 15:01:09 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Start of the Journey.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 1 Gender Aptitude/Date created: 2012-02-06 17:52:50 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-06 17:52:50 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- There and Back Again.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/There And Back Again/Date created: 2009-03-24 20:24:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-04-08 15:04:21 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- DIVA questions Pages09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Date created: 2015-12-13 14:12:40 EST-0500Date modified: 2015-12-13 14:12:40 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- book 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/for alan/Date created: 2011-09-07 15:08:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-07 15:08:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Brown Reader Bornstein (edited2).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Brown Anthology/Date created: 2013-06-10 19:49:53 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-06-10 19:49:53 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- The Same Page BC PASS.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Book/0. to be sorted/Date created: 2017-04-04 15:56:49 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-04 15:56:49 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 6 Sex Sex Sex Changes Accepted.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2013-09-07 12:33:13 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-09-07 12:34:22 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- ASU SORC Speaker Template.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/ASU Feb 2010/Date created: 2009-12-17 22:14:10 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-12-17 22:14:10 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Princess Proposal 2.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/The Princess Book/Date created: 2011-08-09 12:29:02 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-09 12:32:11 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MS-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~~Copy Editing QPD~~/Date created: 2011-10-28 15:36:43 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-11-02 23:10:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- gotngdraft 4-Jan-2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-01-05 14:59:30 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-14 11:25:28 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- For the Fun of It Intro 3.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Book/0. to be sorted/Date created: 2017-03-11 15:12:03 EST-0500Date modified: 2017-03-11 15:12:03 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 9/Date created: 2012-05-29 18:17:51 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-30 17:28:33 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass 7x9.pages